Food Darzee - Key to your health                  

menu

Privacy Policy
==============

### 1\. INTRODUCTION

Thank you for choosing us.

This document, i.e., Privacy Policy ("**Policy**") contains the manner and details in which **3CAD Hospitality LLP** that owns and controls the brands known as 'Food Darzee, Coached Darzee and Baked Darzee ("**we**", "**us**", "**our**") collects and processes the data that you, the user ("**user**", "**you**", "**your**") of this platform ("**Platform**") provide to us. 3CAD Hospitality LLP is a limited liability partnership incorporated under the Limited Liabilities Partnership Act, 2008 in India and having its registered office at 207,Veena Beena Shopping Centre, Turner Road, Bandra (West), Suburban Mumbai – 400050.

We may change the terms of this Policy from time to time. Please check this page regularly for updates. In the event that there are material changes to the Policy, we may send you additional notice by way of an e-mail or a notification on the Platform.

While we aim to be completely transparent in the manner we choose to protect your privacy, you may not agree with the terms of this Policy. Should this be the case, please remember it is your choice whether you wish to continue using our Services and Platform.

This Policy and the Terms of Use are to be read in consonance and form part of a single understanding. Any capitalised terms not defined herein shall be interpreted to mean as defined in the Terms of Use.

### 2\. INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU ON THE WEBSITE

| Type of user data | Purpose for collecting and processing this data | When do we collect this data? |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Name<br><br>Phone<br><br>Number<br><br>E-mail ID<br><br>Address<br><br>Age | For delivery of your meal (Food Darzee) or food order (Baked Darzee) or providing consultation services (Coached Darzee) | We ask you for this information when you –<br><br>(1) Subscribe to any of our packages or plans for availing our services on Food Darzee or Coached Darzee;<br><br>(2) At the “checkout” stage from where you proceed to pay for your order on Baked Darzee. |
| Age<br><br>Physical and mental Health<br><br>Medical History | To create personalised diet plan while rendering our nutritional services under Food Darzee and Coached Darzee. | We ask for these details when you speak to our nutritionist and/or subscribe to our nutrition plan on Food Darzee or Coached Darzee. |
| Password | To create an account on the Baked Darzee platform | At the "checkout" stage from where you proceed to pay for your order on Baked Darzee. |
| Payment Information | We do not collect or store your payment information. In the event you choose to "save card details for future transactions", our payment gateway may collect and store your payment information. | At the "checkout" stage from where you proceed to pay for your order. |

The above list of data being collected is a non-exhaustive list and we may require you to share further information from time to time for which we will notify you.

### 3\. INFORMATION THAT IS GENERATED BY YOU WHILE USING THE WEBSITE

| Type of usage data | Purpose for collecting and processing this data | When do we collect this data? |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Data and inferred data about how you interact with the Platform including but not limited to the products you show interest in, your search queries, the text and content you input on the Platform, the location from where you access the Platform. | Legitimate interests in relation to inferences about your interests which we use in our business to tailor and improve the Services. Where cookies are used for such processing (as explained below), we obtain prior consent where required under applicable laws. | The information related to your usage of the Platform is collected automatically and in a dynamic manner as and when you use the Platform. |
|     |     |     |

### 4\. TECHNICAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE

| Type of data | Purpose for collecting and processing this data | When do we collect this data? |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Information about the types of devices you are using such as unique device IDs, network connection type; provider, network and device performance browser type; information enabling digital rights management; operating system, and the version of the Platform. | Legitimate interests in managing and improving our Services, the Platform and protecting our content. | Technical information is collected automatically and in a dynamic manner as and when you use the Platform. |
|     |     |     |

### 5\. WHY WE COLLECT AND PROCESS PERSONAL DATA AND HOW WE USE IT

* To fulfil buying and selling requests on the Platform.
* To enable our nutritionists to communicate with you and send a personalised diet plan.
* To conduct business planning and forecasting.
* To enable us to diagnose and identify any technical advancements or troubleshoot issues.
* For marketing and advertising purposes.
* To answer your questions or requests for information or handle your complaints.
* To ensure that content provided regarding our Services is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other devices.
* To notify you about updates or changes to our Services or Platform features and content.
* To provide you with promotional communications, to the extent that you have provided consent to receive such communications under applicable law.
* To comply with legal obligations and requests by law enforcement.
* To establish, exercise, or defend legal claims.
* Inferences drawn from your browsing patterns help us understand your preferences better, thereby allowing us to offer a more focused range of products and optimise our Services.
* Inferences drawn from how you interact with the Platform allow us to constantly identify what we could do better to help our users.
* To detect, investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions and other illegal activities and protect the rights and property of 3CAD Hospitality LLP.  

### 6\. ANALYTICS TECHNOLOGIES

Tracking Technologies

1. 3CAD Hospitality LLP and our analytics partners use tracking technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts.
2. We may use any of the following categories of cookies on our Platform as detailed below. Each cookie falls within one of these four categories:
    
    | Type of Cookies | Description |
    | --- | --- |
    | Essential Cookies | Essential cookies (first-party cookies) are sometimes called “strictly necessary” as without them we cannot provide many services that you need on the Platform. For example, essential cookies help remember your preferences as you move around the Platform.. |
    | Analytics Cookies | These cookies track information about Platform visits so we can make improvements and report our performance. For example, we analyse visitor and user behaviour to provide more relevant content or suggest certain activities. These cookies collect information about how visitors use the Platform, which site the user came from, the number of each user’s visits, and how long a user stays on the Platform. We might also use analytics cookies to test new ads, pages, or features to see how users react to them. |
    | Functionality or Preference Cookies | During your visit to the Platform, these cookies are used to remember information you have entered or choices you make such as your username, language, or region. They also store your preferences when personalizing the Platform to optimize your use of the Platform. These preferences are remembered through the use of persistent cookies, and the next time you visit the Platform you won’t have to set them again. |
    | Targeting or Advertising Cookies | These third-party cookies are placed by third-party advertising platforms or networks in order to deliver ads and track ad performance. They may subsequently use information about your visit to show you ads that you may be interested in our Platform and other websites. For example, these cookies remember which browsers have visited the Platform. |
    
3. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you choose not to activate cookies or to later disable them, you can still visit our Platform, but your ability to use some features may be limited.
4. Web beacons, tags, and scripts may be used on the Platform or in e-mails to help us deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and advertising campaign effectiveness, and determine whether an e-mail has been opened and clicked on. We may receive reports based on the use of the aforesaid technologies by our service/analytics providers on an individual and aggregated basis.
5. We partner with third parties, such as Google Analytics, to manage the advertising of our brand on other sites or platforms as well as across other devices you use, based on your past visits to our Platform. Our third-party partners such as Google Ads and Facebook Ads may use tracking technologies to gather data about your activities on our Platform to deliver such advertising to you, including retargeting ads.
6. We may use third-party trackers to let us know when users have visited the Platform by “clicking-through” our sponsored advertising or content hosted on third-party platforms. The Platform uses Google Analytics code to gather statistical data. These cookies help us accurately estimate the number of visitors on the Platform and the volume of usage of the Platform. This is done, inter alia, to ensure that the Platform is available and running efficiently even with maximum traffic.
7. In the event you seek to opt-out of this tracking, please contact us at [inquiries@fooddarzee.com](mailto:inquiries@fooddarzee.com). Please note that this does not opt you out of being served advertisements. You may continue to receive generic ads on these third-party platforms. You may also opt-out of receiving advertisements across devices by adjusting your ad preference in your relevant device account, Google account, or Apple account.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain data and automatically store it in log files. This data may include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. These and the open statistics are used in aggregate form to give us an indication of the popularity of the content and to help us make decisions about future content and formatting.  

### 7\. SENSITIVE DATA

As per the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practice) Rules, 2011, a certain category of user’s data is classified as “sensitive personal data”. For the sake of clarity, we have provided a table enlisting the type of sensitive personal data 3CAD Hospitality LLP and/or its third-party associates process and/or collect or may process and/or collect such data on the Platform.

| Type of Data | Yes/No |
| --- | --- |
| Password | Yes |
| Financial information including bank account or payment instrument details. | Yes |
| Physical, physiological or mental health condition | Yes |
| Sexual orientation | No  |
| Medical records and history | Yes |

The passwords for accounts created on Baked Darzee are secured using high end encryption. All financial information shared by the users is collected and processed by the payment aggregator associated with us, on the payments page. We do not collect or store your bank details or other financial information.

### 8\. YOUR RIGHTS OVER THE PERSONAL DATA THAT YOU SHARE WITH US

Privacy laws across the world grant individual’s rights over their personal data. These rights allow you to control the personal data that we collect and the manner in which we use it.

| Your rights | Explanation |
| --- | --- |
| Right to confirmation and access | The right to be informed of, and request access to your personal data that is collected and processed by us. |
| Right to correction, rectification, and erasure | The right to request that any incomplete or inaccurate personal data provided be updated, corrected, or erased. |
| Right to restrict | The right to request that we temporarily or permanently stop processing all or some part of the personal data that you provide to us. |
| Right to object | \- The right, at any time, to object to us processing your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation.<br><br>\- The right to object to your personal data being processed for direct marketing purposes. |
| Right to not be subject to automated decision making | The right to not be subject to a decision based on automated decision-making basis the personal data that you share with us. This includes profiling, in the event that such profiling would have a legal effect on you or a similarly significant effect. |

In case of any requests or queries in relation to the above, please contact us at [inquiries@fooddarzee.com](mailto:inquiries@fooddarzee.com)

### 9\. WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR DATA WITH?

From time to time, we may share your personal data with third-parties such as:

* I.T. & e-mail service providers
* Fraud prevention vendors
* Payment processors
* Law enforcement authorities
* Delivery service providers
* Advertising partners
* Data analytics agencies
* Social media partners
* Entities seeking to acquire or invest in 3CAD Hospitality LLP

### 10\. HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR DATA?

We implement appropriate technical and organisational measures to help protect the security of your personal data including pseudonymisation, encryption, access, and retention policies to guard against unauthorised access and unnecessary retention of personal data in our systems. Your password protects your account and therefore we recommend using a strong password that is unique to your account.

### 11\. RETENTION AND DELETION OF DATA

Retention of data: We collect and store your data for only as long as it is necessary for you to operate the Platform. In addition to this, we may also retain your data for legitimate and essential business purposes, including but not limited to making data-driven business decisions, complying with legal obligations, and resolving any disputes that may arise from time to time. Deletion of data: Unless legally allowed or legally mandated to store such data, upon receiving a request from the User, we will delete all your personal data or anonymize it so that such data is no longer identifiable to you as an individual.

### 12\. THIRD-PARTY LINKS

The Platform may contain links to external websites owned and operated by third parties. Please note that when you use third-party services, their own terms of use and privacy policies will govern your use of those services. 3CAD Hospitality LLP does not collect, process, or store any personal data provided by you to such third-party links, including the payment gateway, through the Platform. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these external websites.

### 13\. GOVERNING LAW, JURISDICTION AND ARBITRATION

As provided in our [Terms of Use](https://fooddarzee.com/terms-and-conditions)

### 14\. CONTACT US

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, please feel free to reach out to us by contacting our Grievance Redressal Officer (Mr. Aditya Gupte) at [inquiries@foodarzee.com](mailto:inquiries@foodarzee.com) or +91 9082663088 or by writing to us at the following address:

3CAD Hospitality LLP ,  
207,Veena Beena Shopping Center,  
Turner Road, Bandra (West),  
Suburban Mumbai – 400050.

Have more questions?

 Call on  

 Mail us at  

 For complaints or feedback, email us at  

Food Darzee

Food Darzee

A food and nutrition company that offers healthy and tasty meals to be delivered to your doorstep

3 CAD Hospitality LLP 2024\. | All rights reserved.

Popular articles on food darzee
